http://www.seotops.com/privacy.htm

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how The Internet Marketing Guru uses and protects any personal information that you submit when you contact us.
We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. When you contact us we ask you to provide certain information. You can be assured that this information will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
This policy is effective from June, 2014.
What we collect
We may collect the following personal information:
contact information including your name and email address
What we do with the information we collect
Possible uses of the information include:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our services.
We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Links to other websites
The Internet Marketing Guru website contains links to other websites. We do not have any control over the websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy please contact us.
Home Contact
Privacy
Internet Marketing Guru - Online Marketing in the UK
Site and contents are © Internet Marketing Guru - All Rights Reserved 2014 - 2020
